

Rohit Tagadiya

Software Engineer

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Angular, IONIC, HTML5, Typescript, JavaScript, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap. Strong background in project management.

rohit.tagadiya@gmail.com

💡 9, Hilcrest AL10 8EZ, Hatfield, UK

S live:.cid.5191b82a3fed72e7

🖹 stackoverflow.com/users/12168235/rohit-tagadiya

+44 7442099038

in linkedin.com/in/rohit-tagadiya-22472012b

github.com/rohittagadiya

• medium.com/@rohit.tagadiya

WORK EXPERIENCE

Angular Software Engineer for SaaS AppSmartPass

05/2022 - Present

Pennsylvania, United States

SmartPass is the ultimate solution for hallway management. It helps increase time in class, makes your school safer, and curbs vandalism.

Tasks

- Adding new features to support new functionality on the apps and website.
- Implement bug fixes

Angular front end developer InfoSecEnforcer | essert

01/2022 - 05/2022

SANTA CLARA, CA, USA

We provide software for California privacy compliance & to prevent data breaches. We help avoid penalties and lawsuits.

Tasks

- Developed new UI of SaaS product
- Manage all front-end side responsibilities

Front-end developer Optimumbrew Technology

07/2019 - 01/2022

Surat, India

Product base company. Developing editor type products. like Image editor and video editor apps and web

Tasks

- Working as front-end developer in <u>PhotoADKing</u>
- Implement Intro/Outro module in PhotoADKing.
- Implement fastspring payment integration in PhotoADKing.

EDUCATION

MSc Artificial Intelligence and Robotics University of Hertfordshire

09/2022 - Present

Hatfield, UK

Surat, India

Information Technology GTU, SCET

08/2014 - 05/2018

SKILLS

Front-end developing

Project management

Complex problem solver

Strong decision maker

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

Angular, Ionic, Typescript, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Flutter

Application Tools

Visual Studio code, Visual Studio, Turbo C, Net-beans, MS Office, Eclipse

Operating systems

Windows, Ubuntu, macOS

LANGUAGES

Enalish

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

PROJECTS LINK

https://photoadking.com/qr-code-generator

https://essert.io/

https://smartpass.app